<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.objectstyle.wolips.maven"
      label="%feature.featureName"
      version="1.0.6"
      provider-name="%feature.providerName"
      image="%feature.image">

   <description url="http://objectstyle.org/confluence/display/WOL/Home">
      %feature.description
   </description>

   <copyright>
      %feature.copyright
   </copyright>

   <license>
      /*
 * ====================================================================
 * 
 * The ObjectStyle Group Software License, Version 1.0
 * 
 * Copyright (c) 2006 - 2007 The ObjectStyle Group and individual authors of the
 * software. All rights reserved.
 * 
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
 * 
 * 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
 * this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 * 
 * 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
 * this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
 * and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 * 
 * 3. The end-user documentation included with the redistribution, if any, must
 * include the following acknowlegement: &quot;This product includes software
 * developed by the ObjectStyle Group (http://objectstyle.org/).&quot; Alternately,
 * this acknowlegement may appear in the software itself, if and wherever such
 * third-party acknowlegements normally appear.
 * 
 * 4. The names &quot;ObjectStyle Group&quot; and &quot;Cayenne&quot; must not be used to endorse or
 * promote products derived from this software without prior written permission.
 * For written permission, please contact andrus@objectstyle.org.
 * 
 * 5. Products derived from this software may not be called &quot;ObjectStyle&quot; nor
 * may &quot;ObjectStyle&quot; appear in their names without prior written permission of
 * the ObjectStyle Group.
 * 
 * THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES,
 * INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
 * FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
 * OBJECTSTYLE GROUP OR ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
 * INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
 * LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA,
 * OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
 * LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
 * NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
 * EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
 * ====================================================================
 * 
 * This software consists of voluntary contributions made by many individuals on
 * behalf of the ObjectStyle Group. For more information on the ObjectStyle
 * Group, please see http://objectstyle.org/.
 *  
 */
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="%feature.updateSiteName"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.objectstyle.wolips.ui" version="1.0.6" match="perfect"/>
      <import plugin="org.objectstyle.wolips.workbenchutilities" version="1.0.6" match="perfect"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.objectstyle.wolips.baseforplugins" version="1.0.6" match="perfect"/>
      <import plugin="org.objectstyle.wolips.baseforuiplugins" version="1.0.6" match="perfect"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.objectstyle.wolips.maven.core"
         download-size="8"
         install-size="8"
         version="1.0.6"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.objectstyle.wolips.maven.launching"
         download-size="8"
         install-size="8"
         version="1.0.6"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.objectstyle.wolips.maven.ui"
         download-size="8"
         install-size="8"
         version="1.0.6"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
