<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
    <title>Success Stories</title>

    <properties>
        <author>Ulrich Koester</author>
    </properties>

    <body>        
    	<section name="Success Stories">        
        	<subsection name="Christian Edward Gruber">
        		<p>We started using WO5.1 on Windows, and I was all like WO RUlEZ!  Only it
				became quite apparent, that Project Builder hadn't evolved in any
				significant way since WO4, at least on Windows.  Eclipse and WOLips made
				it so easy.  I can still use WOBuilder and EOModeler, but with WOLips
				and WOProject, my employees can use WebObjects from within Eclipse.
				This makes our new WO projects first class developer citizens alongside
				our J2EE older (maintainence) projects.

				In short, WOLips staved off developer revolt, and allowed me to pursue a
				WebObjects strategy unimpeded by Apple's lagging IDE.</p>
        	</subsection>
        	<subsection name="Ian McDougall">
        		<p>I've been working with WebObjects since 1997.  My development platform has
				primarily been Windows, and I was disappointed year after year that the
				Project Builder was not keeping up with modern IDE's.  After Debugging was
				removed in WO5, I decided to stick with 4.5 until a decent IDE was released.

				Then along came WOProject and WOLips and I decided to take the leap from
				Project Builder to Eclipse.  The transition was quite easy, with the switch
				from 4.5 to 5.1 being the most difficult part.  Now I've moved all
				developers here over to Eclipse and WOLips, and things couldn't be better.
				I haven't come across a single reason to fire up PBWO since switching.

				Thank you from everyone here for your effort in this area.  You've filled a
				gap that WebObjects developers have had for years!</p>
        	</subsection>
        	<subsection name="Colin Clark">
        		<p>I thought I'd share my WOProject success story with you. Here goes:

				As the technical lead for the University of Toronto's CourseView Project, a 
				large institutional service tasked with the collection and distribution of 
				information about all our course offerings, I chose WebObjects 5 for its fantastic
				persistence framework and its elegant use of design patterns. However, I wasn't 
				well-prepared for the abysmal state of the WO development tools on Windows. One 
				of the fundamental requirements of the project has been to support flexible, 
				cross-platform development in a Java-centric environment. This goal was virtually 
				impossible to achieve using the out-of-the-box WebObjects tools on Windows.

				In order to work around these problems and to introduce the use of continuous 
				integration and agile development techniques, we decided to write our own set 
				of build scripts using Ant. The WOProject tasks for Ant have become a central 
				aspect of our build environment from unit testing to development to final deployment. 
				This change to our development process has enabled us to respond more effectively to 
				the constant change inherent in software projects. It has also ensured that development
				on Windows continues to be a viable option for our developers,
				fully independently of  ProjectBuilder!</p>
        	
        	</subsection>
        	<subsection name="Anjo Krank and Patrice Gautier from the ProjectWonder team">
        		<p>On Windows, WOLips' advantages are obvious, but even on OS X it is beneficial.
        		Apple's pbxbuild may be sufficient for small projects, but <a href="http://wonder.sourceforge.net/">Project Wonder</a>
        		consist of a large number of subprojects. Short turnaround times and reliable
        		multi-stage interdependent builds are mandatory. Early tests with ant and woproject
        		revealed that - with proper file layout - it is not only an order of magnititude
        		faster, but also allows for template-based builds. Just drop your files in a certain
        		structure and set a few flags and off you go. WOProject is a great way to build your WO apps!</p>
        	</subsection>
        </section>
    </body>
</document>
        