<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
    <title>Overview</title>

    <properties>
        <author>Andrei Adamchik</author>
    </properties>

    <body>        
        <!-- Welcome section -->
        <section name="Welcome to WOProject and WOLips">

        <p><i>July 8, 2003.</i> <b>WOProject release 1.0.4 is out.</b></p>
        <p>Download a new <a href="compatibilty_matrix.html">release</a> of WOProject.
        <hr/>
        </p>
        
        <p><i>July 8, 2003.</i> <b>WOLips 1.0.4 released. This is bugfix release to solve a classpath problem in 1.0.2.</b></p>
        <p>WOLips is a plugin for <a href="http://eclipse.org">Eclipse IDE</a> that
        support development of WebObjects applications and frameworks.
        <ul>
            <li>To find the correct version <a href="compatibilty_matrix.html">click</a> here.</li>
            <li><a href="wolips_install.html">How to install via Update Manager.</a></li>
        </ul>
        <hr/>
        </p>
                       
        <p><i>September 2, 2002.</i> <b>Start-Script Lobotomy.</b></p>
        <p>Read <a href="articles/WOFLobotomy1/index.html">an article</a> by Reimer Mellin on an easy way 
        to deploy WebObjects 5.x applications. To download WOStart code discussed in the
        article, use <a href="http://objectstyle.org/downloads/woproject/WOStart.zip">this 
        link</a>.
        <hr/>
        </p>
        
        <p>Welcome to WOProject project page. WOProject provides a set of tools to work 
        with WebObjects 5.1 independent from platform and IDE. Even though Apple is doing a
        great job maintaining cross-platform development tools, for obvious reasons support 
        for such tools on platforms other than Mac has been declining over the years. At the
        same time in Java world new technologies have emerged that allow to organize 
        and build projects with code, resources and documentation in an IDE-independent 
        fashion. WOProject includes all necessary support to take advantage of these 
        technologies (namely 
        <a href="http://jakarta.apache.org/ant/index.html">Ant</a>). Even people using
        latest and greatest ProjectBuilder on Mac may find it useful to organize 
        their code in a portable manner, and speed up their build process.</p>
        
        <p>With 1.0 release of WOProject IDE independence is finally achieved. WebObjects 
        developers can build both frameworks and applications, as well as generate Java 
        classes using Ant. WOProject philosophy is to allow developers to use project 
        structure compatible with ProjectBuilder, or any other structure they desire.</p>
        
        
         
        <p>Other aspects of WOProject are integration of WebObjects NSLog's with 
        <a href="http://jakarta.apache.org/log4j/index.html">Log4J
        logging framework</a>, database plugins and other WebObjects utilities.</p>
        </section>
        
        <section name="Contribute to WOProject">
        <p>WOProject is opensource and is shipped under apache-style <a href="LICENSE">license</a>. 
        Code contributions, patches and other input from WebObjects developer community
        are welcomed.</p>
 		</section>
 		
 	    <section name="Contact Us">
        <p>If you have questions about WOProject or suggestions on how to fix/improve
        its features, post a message on <a href=
        "http://objectstyle.org/woproject/lists.html">woproject-dev 
        mailing list</a>. This is the best way to get help from WOProject creators 
        and user community.</p>
 		</section>
    </body>
</document>
